■
声明：本字幕由YYeTs人人影视字幕组原创翻译制作
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎登录人人影视论坛交流 下载 在线观看 www.YYeTs.net
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：小帝 66 战 螃蟹 思思 paradise 妞妞
校对：何何 思思 螃蟹 战 美景 小帝时间轴：YY吕伟 leolou
========== 字幕总监制：何何   ==========
不得已而为之的最后一招
It's a measure of last resort.
你会进入那个温室
You're gonna go into that greenhouse.
乘电梯去真正的兰花站
The elevator takes you down to the actual orchid station.
不好意思  伙计  但你好像没有
I'm sorry, man, but maybe I missed the part
跟我说怎么才能解决
Where you explained what I'm supposed to do
-里面的武装分子  -我跟你说过多少次了  John?
-About the armed men inside. -How many times do I have to tell you, John?
我总有计划
I always have a plan.
这些不是Jack或Sawyer留下的
These aren't Jack or Sawyer.
不管你是谁  马上出来!
Whoever you are, come out now!
我是Benjamin Linus  相信你们一直在找我
My name is Benjamin Linus. I believe you're looking for me.
女士们先生们  大洋815航班的幸存者
Ladies and gentlemen, the survivors of oceanic 8-1-5.
Jarrah先生  还有没有
Mr. Jarrah, is it possible
其他在飞机失事后的幸存者
There are any other survivors from the crash
仍未被发现?
Yet to be discovered?
不  绝对没有
No, absolutely not.
为什么给我打电话  Jack?
Why did you call me, Jack?
我希望你已经听说
I was hoping that you'd heard,
你也许得去参加葬礼
That maybe you'd go to the funeral.
我为什么要去参加葬礼?
Why would I go to the funeral?
不会有什么改变的...
This is not gonna change--
不  我已经厌倦了...终日的谎言
No, I'm sick... of lying.
我得走了
I have to go.
-他会担心我去哪了  -别...
-He's gonna be wondering where I am-- -Don't...
我们不应该离开那
We were not supposed to leave.
不  我们应该
Yes, we were.
再见  Jack
Good-bye, Jack.
我们得回去  Kate
We have to go back, Kate.
我们得回去!
We have to go back!
我们得回去?
"we have to go back"?
-等等...  -你觉得自己是谁?!
Now hold on-- who do you think you are?!
你在这两天里不停的给我打电话
You call me over and over again for two days straight,
尽说些疯话!
Stoned on your pills!
然后你拿着Jeremy Bentham的讣告来这
And then you show up here with an obituary for Jeremy Bentham.
当他来找我  我得知我们必须说
When he came to me and I heard what we had to say,
我知道他已经疯了
I knew he was crazy.
但你...你相信他
But you... you believed him.
是的  相信他  胜过任何人
Yes. Him, of all people.
是的  Kate  我是
Yes, Kate, I did,
因为他说  那是唯一的办法
Because he said that that was the only way
能保证你的安全  你和Arron的安全
That I could keep you safe-- you and Arron.
别提他的名字
Don't you say his name.
我还是要给他解释
I still have to explain to him
当时你为什么不在那给他读书
Why you are not there to read to him,
所以别提他的名字!
So don't you say his name!
对不起
I'm sorry.
在过去三年里
I've spent the last three years
我尽力试图忘掉那些自从我们离开那天起
Trying to forget all the horrible things
所发生的可怕的事
That happened on the day that we left.
你还有什么资格要我回去?
How dare you ask me to go back?
你确定我们的方位是对的吗?
You sure we're going the right way?
Lapidus说他们朝东北走
Lapidus said they were headed northeast.
你最好走慢点
You might wanna slow down a little,
-因为你看起来象要跌倒  医生  -我很好
-Cause you look like you're about to keel over Doc. -I'm fine.
当然你很好  你总是很好
Of course you're fine. you're always fine.
是那儿吗?
Is this it?
我不知道
I don't know.
现在怎么办  大摇大摆的过去?
So what's the plan, sundance?
我们等到...
The plan is we wait till--
Hugo?
Sawyer!
你还好吧?
You all right?
伙计  你回来了  你怎么知道我在这儿?
Dude, you came back. how'd you know where I was?
见到你真好  Hurley
It's good to see you, Hurley.
是啊
Yeah.
是啊  伙计  见到你也很好
Yeah, man. you, too.
他到底在哪?
So where the hell is he?
Locke!
你好  Jack
Hello, Jack.
这儿的C4炸药
There's enough c4 here
能把一艘航母炸掉
To blow up a bloody aircraft carrier.
当我在军队服役时...
When I was in the army...
我做过六个月的爆破军械处理
I did six months explosive ordnance disposal,
就像俗话说的
Which, as the saying goes,
这段时间正好让你学会怎么把自己炸飞
Is just enough time to learn how to blow yourself up.
有计时器吗?  怎么还没爆炸?
Is it on a timer? And why hasn't it gone off yet?
这是个收音机  这是...
This is a-a radio receiver. It's...
就像个步话机
It's like a walkie-talkie.
你给他发送个信号  然后...
You send it a signal, and, uh...
就会远程引爆炸弹
It--it triggers the bomb remotely.
那我们能不能...
So can we...
关掉它?
Turn off?
这是个...
This is a...
这是拉发线  移动一下就会...爆炸
This is a trip wire. Move it, and... boom.
这是伪装线  要是剪错了...
This is dummy wiring. If you cut the wrong one...
爆炸
Boom.
这是多重线圈引爆系统
This is multiple firing systems.
损毁一个  另一个就会...爆炸
You disable one, the next one... boom.
这个...电池是能量来源
Um, this... battery's the power source.
如果你卸下它...爆炸
If you disconnect it... boom.
你在这儿干嘛?
What are you doing in here?
这下面有一个达摩站
There's a-a dharma station below us,
我在找条进去的路
And, um, I'm looking for a way to get in.
进去干嘛?
Get in and do what?
Hugo  James  不介意我和Jack单独谈谈吧?
Hugo, James, would you mind if I spoke to Jack alone?
不用了  我们回来只是找Hurley的
Don't bother. We just came back for Hurley.
走吧
Let's go.
-Jack  你得听我跟你说  -不  我要做的是...
-Jack, you need to hear what I have to say-- -no, what I need to do
回到直升机那  上飞机
Is to walk back to the chopper, get on it,
然后把其他人带离这个岛
And get the rest of our people off this island.
伙计  这可不是现在最好的选择
Uh, dude, probably not the best idea right now.
那些军人正把Ben押往那个直升机
Those rambo guys are taking Ben to that helicopter.
一小时前Ben向他们投降了
He surrendered himself to 'em about an hour ago.
他为什么那样做?
Now why the hell would he do that?
告诉我  Ben
So tell me something, ben.
你为什么就这么重要?
What is it that makes you so important, hmm?
我很好奇
I'm curious.
我很好奇为什么
I'm curious as to why
Widmore先生肯给我那么多钱
Mr. Widmore would pay me so much money
让我来这抓你
Just to come out here and capture you
再把你活着带回去
And bring you back alive.
Charles widmore让你杀了我女儿?
Charles widmore tell you to kill my daughter?
你怎么拿到工具箱的?
How'd he get the toolbox?
妈的
Damn.
谁给你拿的工具箱  Frank?
Who gave you the toolbox,Frank?
就待在那
You're good right there.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是Kate
I'm kate.
我是815航班上的一员
I'm one of the passengers of flight 815.
你干嘛要跑?
Why are you running?
有人追我...他的人
I'm being chased... by his people.
Kocol  lacour  看好Flank
Kocol... lacour... redfern on Flank.
过来
Whoa. Hey. Come here.
跪下
Get on your knees.
你们都给我双手抱头
Hands above your heads, both of you.
射击!
Now! spray it!
Ben  跟紧了
Ben, stay close.
快跑!
Run!
快跑
Run.
手雷!
Grenade!
起来  快起来
Get up. come on. get up.
谢谢你能来  Richard
Thank you for coming, richard.
是我的荣幸
My pleasure.
你能帮我解开吗  Kate?
Could you cut me free, kate?
是什么协议?
What was the arrangement?
他们帮我们救你  然后我们让他们离开这个岛
They, uh, help us free you, and we let 'em off the island.
很公平
Fair enough.
直升机是你们的了
The helicopter is yours.
你和Sayid能安全回去了
You and sayid have a safe journey back.
那么我们能走了?
So we can go?
离开这个岛?
Off the island?
就这样吗?
That's it?
就这样
That's it.
谢谢你  小姐
Thank you, miss.
你是Hruley吗?
Are you hurley?
是的
Yeah.
你很危险吗?
Are you dangerous?
抱歉  我认识你吗?
I'm sorry. do I know you?
不  你不认识我...  不过你认识我孙子
No, you don't know me... but you know my grandson.
我们跋山涉水
Now we've traveled all the way across country
就是为了他能来见你
Just so he could see you.
我得知道你会不会干些疯事
I need to know if you're gonna do anything crazy.
我不会做什么疯狂的事
I won't do anything crazy.
Walt
Hey, walt.
Hurley
Hey, hurley.
你长大了  伙计
You're getting big, dude.
你知道  当你们回来的时候
You know, when you came back,
我一直在盼望你们中有人能来看我
I was waiting for one of you to come see me,
不过...  没有人来
But... nobody did.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你知道后来谁来看我了吗?
Do you know who did come see me?
Jeremy Bentham
Jeremy bentham.
我不明白你们为什么要撒谎
I don't understand why you're all lying.
我们撒谎...
We're lying...
是因为只有这样才能保护
Because it's the only way to protect everyone
其他没有回来的人
That didn't come back.
就像我爸爸?
Like my dad?
就像你爸爸  是的
Like your dad, yeah.
他们到底在那说什么?
What the hell they talkin' about in there, anyway?
我不知道  领导权问题?
I don't know. leader stuff?
你从哪弄的?
Where'd you get that?
Ben从地下挖出的盒子里的  还不错
Came from a box ben dug up out of the ground. they're good.
谢谢你回来找我
Thanks for coming back for me.
你值得的
Ah, you got it.
Claire和她的婴儿都还好吧?
Claire and the baby okay?
你想跟我说什么  John?
What did you wanna talk to me about, john?
我想你能重新考虑下离开这个岛  Jack
I want you to reconsider leaving the island, jack.
我想你留下来
I would like you to stay.
你想我留下来
You'd like me to stay.
是的  就是这样
Yeah, that's right.
你飞了一把匕首
You threw a knife
插在了一个没有武装的女人背后
Into the back of an unarmed woman.
你带着我们一半的人横穿过这个岛
You led half of our people across the island
而让他们大多数都被杀了
And got most of them killed.
Jack  你用枪指着我脑袋
Well, jack, you put a gun to my head
然后你扣下了扳机
And you pulled the trigger.
我希望我们能让过去的都过去了
I was hoping we could let bygones be bygones.
我跟你说
Well, I'll tell you what.
你就待在这个小温室里好了
You stay here in your little greenhouse,
不过我们其余人的要回家了
But the rest of us are going home.
不过你不应该回家
But you're not supposed to go home.
那我到底应该做什么?
And what am I supposed to do?
我想我还记得
Oh, I think I remember.
在回到舱门的路上你说的是什么
What was it that you said on the way out to the hatch--
那个坠机是我们的宿命?
That crashing here was our destiny?
你知道的  Jack  你知道你在这儿是有原因的
You know, jack. you know that you're here for a reason.
你知道的
You know it.
而如果你离开这里
And if you leave this place,
那种原因就会从你的内心开始
That knowledge is gonna eat you alive
慢慢吞噬你...
From the inside out...
直到你决定回来
Until you decide to come back.
再见  John
Good-bye, john.
你要对他们撒谎
You're gonna have to lie.
什么?
Excuse me?
如果你不得不走
If you have to go,
那么你不得不对所有的事情撒谎...
Then you have to lie about everything...
自从我们来到这个岛上发生的所有事情
Everything that happened since we got to the island.
这是唯一能保护它的办法
It's the only way to protect it.
这只是个岛  John
It's an island, john.
没有人需要保护它
No one needs to protect it.
这不是个岛
It's not an island.
这是个奇迹发生的地方
It's a place where miracles happen.
如果...如果你不相信
And--and--if you-- if you don't believe that,
Jack  如果你不能相信的话
Jack, if you can't believe that,
那你在这里等着  看我要做的事吧
Just wait till you see what I'm about to do.
世上根本就没有奇迹
There's no such thing as miracles.
我们就看看到底谁是对的
We'll just have to see which one of us is right.
我打扰了吗?
Am I interrupting?
很高兴看见你  Jack
Nice to see you, too, jack.
找不到安祖花  是吗?
Couldn't find the anthuriums, could you?
我不知道它们长什么样
I don't know what they look like.
你们在干什么?
What are you doing?
你没有告诉他吗?
Didn't you tell him?
我试了
I tried.
Sayid和Kate正在直升机那等你
Sayid and kate are waiting for you at the helicopter.
我知道你们从海滩来的人
I understand that your people from the beach
-就在我们说话的时候正在被送往货船  -什么?
Are being brought to the freighter even as we speak. what?
我很愿意告诉所有的细节  Jack
I'd love to fill you in on everything you missed, jack,
不过你  Hugo  James  你们需要离开了
But you, hugo, james, you need to get moving.
如果我是你  我会很想在一小时内到船上的
If I were you, I'd want to be on that boat within the hour.
再见  Jack  走吧
Good-bye, jack. let's go.
跟他们说谎  Jack
Lie to them, jack.
如果你对自己都撒谎的话
If you do it half as well as you lie to yourself,
他们会相信你的
They'll believe you.
Michael  下面出什么事了?
Michael? what's going on down there?
准备走了?
Ready to go?
你有告诉其他人吗?
Did you tell anybody?
没有  没说
No, michael. i-i didn't.
能...能关掉吗?
Can you... t-turn it off?
还没开呢
It isn't even on yet.
但...当然  如果水槽里的
But, yeah, if what's in this tank
东西起作用的话
Does what it's supposed to do,
我们就没事了
We're gonna be okay.
听着  我会让Jin到上面来
Look, I'll send jin upstairs.
他应该在上面陪你
There's no need for him to be down there with me
没必要在下面把时间浪费在我身上
When he can be up here with you.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
恭喜你  Sun
Congratulations, sun.
-你要干什么?  -把它冻起来
You're gonna what? freeze it.
这是液化氮
This is liquid nitrogen.
我们可以用它来冷藏
We use it in the refrigeration hold.
炸弹需要充电才能引爆  对吧?
The bomb needs a charge from the battery to detonate, right?
而电池则需要化学反应才能有电
And the battery runs on a-a chemical reaction.
把液化氮喷在电池上  让它处于低温状态
I spray the battery. I can keep it cold.
就不会发生化学反应
No reaction.
那现在的问题是?
And what's the catch?
问题是我们只有一罐
The catch is we only have one canister.
用完了  我们就等于回到了最开始
We use it up, we're right back where we started.
那我们是不是应该等到灯变红再用?
Well, shouldn't we save it till the light turns red?
如果等灯变红了
If we see that light turn red
而电池又还到需要的温度以下
And the battery's not already cold,
那红灯就是我们在世界上看到的最后的东西了
That is the last thing we will ever see.
无论怎样  至少我们这样有个预兆
Either way, at least we'll have a warning,
为我们赢得一点时间
Buy ourselves some time.
好吧  把电池先冻起来
All right, um, freeze the battery.
Jin  帮我找这些线的源头
Jin, help me trace back these wires,
列出每一根线的走向
Make a list of where each of them goes to.
船!
Boat!
谢谢
Thank you.
-下来  -你把他们都送上船了吗?
Down there. did you get them all to the boat?
-是的  都平安到达了  -他们往这儿来了吗?
Yeah, everybody's safe. are they coming closer?
他们修好引擎  就会尽量往这里开
They fixed the engine, and they're gonna get as close
开到撞不到暗礁的地方
To the island as they can without hitting the reef,
所以下一批不会花太久时间
So the next trip shouldn't take so long.
我去喝点水
I'm just gonna get some water,
-马上回来  -我让第二组准备出发
And I'll come back in a minute. okay, I'll get the next group ready to go.
-谢了  -Dan!
Thank you. dan!
-怎么?  -谢谢你帮我们
Yeah? thanks for helping us.
这算什么
Absolutely.
好了  出发
Okay, let's go!
谁允许你吃花生的?
Uh, who told you you could eat those peanuts?
那我...我能吃这些花生吗?
May--may I eat these peanuts?
我会盯着你的  小矮子
I'm gonna keep my eye on you, shorty.
-Miles...  -你脖子怎么了?
Miles... somethin' wrong with your neck?
-跟着我  -Dan  你回来了
Follow me, please. dan, you're back.
怎么了
Hey. what's wrong?
我离开十分钟  送下一组人到轮船上去
I'm leaving in ten minutes to take the next group of people
你们必须保证和我一起在船上
To the freighter. you need to make sure that you're with me
不用担心我  我留下来
On that raft, all right? well, don't worry about me, cause I'm gonna stay.
Miles  不不
Miles, no, uh, uh,
我想我还没把...
I don't think I'm getting across the... direness
事态的紧急跟你说明白
Of the circumstance.
不  你说得够明白了  但我还是得留下
Oh, no, you're very dire, but I'm still gonna stay.
十分钟后
Hey, ten minutes.
好的
Yep.
我很惊讶你竟然会走
I'm surprised you wanna leave.
太奇怪了
It's just weird.
在你花了那么多时间
You know, after all that time you spent
好不容易回到这儿后
Trying to get back here.
你说的"回到这儿"  是什么意思?
What do you mean, get back here?
我什么意思?
What do I mean?
这儿到底有多深?
How deep is the station?
很深
Deep.
这就是魔法盒?
Is this the magic box?
不  John  那不是
No, john, it's not.
这些都是干什么的?
What is all this stuff for?
和其他达摩站里的东西差不多...
Same things that all the dharma stations are for...
都是为了那些愚蠢的实验
Silly experiments.
什么样的实验?
What kind of experiments?
你知道吗  John?
You know what, john?
你为什么不看看这卷"扫盲带"
Why don't you watch this very informative video
可能可以回答一些你的问题
That will answer some of your questions?
我要做点别的事
And I'll take care of some business.
你好  我是edgar halliwax博士
Hello. I'm dr. edgar halliwax...
这卷是达摩组织
And this is the orientation film
第六观察站的宣传录像
For station six of the dharma initiative.
你们都知道
As you've no doubt surmised,
第六站  或称之为"兰花站"
Station six, or "the orchid,"
可不是什么植物研究单位
Is not... a botanical research unit.
这个岛上独特的现象
The unique properties...of this island
创造了类似一种喀希米尔的效应
Have created a kind of casimir effect,
也为达摩组织做这些独特的实验提供了条件
Allowing the dharma initiative to conduct unique experiments
而这些实验涉及到空间与时间
In both space and time.
这就是..."传送室"
This... is "the vault,"
建立来通往邻近
Constructed adjacent to a pocket of what we believe... to be
充满带有负电荷的"外来事物"的空间
Negatively charged "exotic matter."
必须要非常小心来避免
Great care must be taken to avoid leaving
房间里有
Inorganic materials...
无机物的残余...
Inside the chamber.
这个岛的电磁能量
The electromagnetic energy within the island
及其的不稳定而且无法预测
Can be highly volatile and unpredictable.
为了您自身
Now for your own safety
和您周围人的安全
And the safety of those around you,
请勿携带金属物品
Metallic objects must never...
进入传送室
Be placed within the vault.
我们初步证实
In our first demonstration,
我们试图将测试主体所在的
We will attempt to shift the test subject
四维空间提前100毫秒
100 milliseconds ahead in four-dimensional space.
此时
Of moments,
动物看似会消失
The animal will seem to disappear,
但事实上...
But in reality...
他的意思是我认为的那样吗?
Uh... was he talking about what I think he was talking about?
如果你是指做时间旅行的兔子  那么的确如此
If you mean time-traveling bunnies, then yes.
你确实知道他强调道
You do know that he said specifically
不能在这里面放任何金属物体?
Not to put anything metal in here.
你在等人?
You expecting someone?
我可以拿回我的武器吗?
May I have my weapon back?
Sayid!
Kate!
见到你真高兴  伙计
Good to see you, dude.
他说什么让你发火了吗?  雀斑女?
He say somethin' to tick you off, freckles?
-他不是我杀的  -那你杀的是哪个?
Didn't kill that one. well, which one did you kill?
孩子在哪儿?
Where's the baby?
和Sun在一起  现在应该在轮船上了
He's with sun, and they should be at the freighter by now.
你还好吧
Are you okay?
现在还好
I am now.
肯尼·洛杰斯
Hey, kenny rogers.
你在干什么?  撬锁?
What you trying to do there, pick a lock?
你有什么更好的主意?
You got a better idea?
钢锯
Hacksaw.
是锯我的手铐吧?
For the handcuffs, right?
来吧
Okay.
放松  没事了  没事了
Take it easy. all right, all right.
Sayid  你怎么回来的?
Sayid, how'd you get back?
我从货轮上搞了只橡皮艇
I took the zodiac from the freighter.
现在安全了吗?
Is it safe?
一具尸体冲上了海岸
A body from the boat washed up on the beach.
现在安全了
It's safe now.
很好
All right!
快离开这鬼地方吧
Let's get the hell outta here!
走了  雀斑女
Let's go, freckles.
我已经受够了这鬼地方了
I've seen enough of this rock.
我们到达之后  还可以回来
After we drop everyone off at the boat, we can come back
-找Claire  对吧?  -当然
And look for claire, right? absolutely.
把手脚都伸回来
Hands and feet inside the vehicle!
起飞了
Let's go for a ride!
我想我有办法了
I think I might have something.
好的  那么  那么如果..
Okay, so... so if...
如果我把这些线切断
If I cut this wire, it...
它就不会与起爆装置相连接
It should disconnect the firing mechanisms.
住手
Stop!
没有好处
No good.
该死的
Damn it!
我知道的还不够
I-i just don't know enough.
我们  我们怎么知道
H-how do we even know
你的小把戏有作用?
Your little freezing trick's doing anything?
只有当灯变红了而我们还活着的时候才知道
We'll know if that light turns red and we're still here.
我们还剩多少?
How much stuff do we have left?
四分之一罐
We got a quarter tank.
如果我们拆不了这炸弹会怎么样?
What happens if we can't deactivate the bomb?
我们最好把所有人从这条船上转移
We better get everybody the hell off this boat.
-怎么了?  -我们在漏油
What's the matter? we're losing fuel.
你说什么?
What?!
我们在漏油
We're losing fuel!
看看外面  告诉我能看见什么
Look outside! tell me if you see anything!
油罐漏了
We have a fuel leak!
子弹一定打穿了油罐
A bullet must have pierced the tank!
-我们要找个地方降落  -不  不能降落
We gotta find a place to set her down! no, don't land!
-为什么?  这岛上没有燃料
What?! there's no fuel on the island!
我们要到船上去  否则这直升机一点用也没有
We've gotta get to the boat, or this chopper's useless!
-我告诉你了  我还没找到船  -那就继续找
I'm telling ya, I don't see the boat! well, then keep looking!
我们得把所有多余的东西
We gotta get every ounce of extra weight
扔下去
Off this chopper now!
所有没用的东西  都扔下去
Anything that's not bolted down, toss it out!
现在怎么样?  够了吗?  我们能到吗?
Now what? is that enough? can we make it?!
我觉得如果
I'd feel a hell of a lot better
能再轻100磅就好多了
If we were a few hundred pounds lighter!
我们离这岛还是很近  能在海滩附近降落
We're still close enough to ditch it on the beach. hey!
别再回那个岛了
Do not go back to the island!
医生  我们可能没有选择了
We might not have a choice, doc.
为什么告诉我这些?
Why are you telling me this?
照我说的做就行了  雀斑女
Just do it, freckles.
Sawyer
Sawyer!
你好   charlotte
Hey, charlotte!
听我说  我想在你上船之前
Listen, uh, I wanted to say
和你说  请...
Before you get on the boat, please--
我想留下  Daniel
I'm gonna stay, daniel...
至少现在想
For now, anyway.
没有  "现在"
There is no "for now."
如果你不跟我一起  "现在就是永远"
If you don't come with me, "for now" could be forever.
没有什么是永远
Nothing's forever.
如果我告诉你   我还在寻找我出生的地方
Would it make any sense if I told you
你会理解吗?
I was still looking for where I was born?
不会
N-no.
再见  daniel
Good-bye, daniel.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
你也不来
You're not coming.
我答应过  不把最后一个人安全送走
I promised I wouldn't leave
不会离开这个岛
Until I got everyone here safely off this island.
别紧张
Relax.
当你回来的时候  我还会在这儿
I'll still be here when you get back.
好吧  好吧
Right, right...
当我回来
When I get back.
好了  大家准备好了吗?
Okay. everybody ready?
我们出发吧
Let's get started.
我们走了
Off we go.
Ben  我知道你在这
I know you're down here, ben.
蜷缩在黑暗的角落
Crouching in the dark,
想给我来个黑枪
Just waiting to take a shot at me.
这是传送室
This... is "the vault"...
Ben  你最好瞄准我的头
Well, you better aim for the head, ben!
就像你的男朋友那样在我背后开枪
You know, like your boyfriend who shot me in the back
就象懦夫一样
Like a coward!
为了避免把非有机物质留在里面
...to avoid leaving inorganic materials inside...
这盔甲
This body armor's, um,
可以同时挡一两颗子弹
Been known to take a bullet or two in its time.
但是Ben  在你射击之前
But before you take your shot, ben,
让我告诉你
Let me tell you about this.
你知道吗?  我已经投了一份人身保险  Ben
See that? I took out a bit of a-a life insurance policy, ben.
那是个心率监测器
It's a heart rate monitor,
它与调频传送器相连
And it's connected to a radio transmitter.
Ben  我们叫它  "死者扳机"
W-we call it a "dead man's trigger," ben.
如果我的心脏停止跳动
If my heart stops beating...
它就会向500磅C4炸药传送信号
It sends a little signal to the 500 pounds of c4
那些炸药我留在了货轮上
That I've got hardwired out there on the freighter
Ben  那样会杀了许多无辜的人
That'd kill a lot of innocent people, ben.
如果你觉得我在虚张声势
If you think I'm bluffing,
那需要我来提醒你
Need I remind you of, uh...
你女儿死的时候的样子吗?
How your daughter looked as she bled out?
脸向下朝着草地
Facedown in the grass?
你又是谁?
Who the hell are you?
我是John Locke
My name is john locke,
我和你无冤无仇
And I have no... conflict with you.
那船上的人也没有
And neither do the people on that boat.
所以...
So...
为什么你不把刀放下?
Why don't you put your knife down?
我们可以谈谈
We can talk about this.
好的  John Locke
Well, john locke...
我从来都靠谈话解决问题
I've never really been one for talk.
你杀了我的女儿
You killed my daughter.
你杀了我女儿
Aah! you killed my daughter!
Ben  停下  不要  停下
Ben! ben! ben, stop! no, no! stop!
Ben  你做了什么?
Ben, what did you do?
你杀了那船上的所有人
You just killed everybody on that boat.
那又怎么样?
So?
==============| YYeTs字幕组招募启示 |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国) 双语字幕校正 时间轴调整
英语翻译 欧美影视新闻翻译 影视评论 论坛版主 美工人员
服务器提供者 发布宣传 联系地址：www.YYeTs.net
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====